interneka.com 2007-09-11

# Interneka Affiliate Program Tracking Software

**Privacy Statement**

Interneka has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Interneka.com

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and is only used by Interneka.

**Advertisers**  
We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we currently do use cookies to save login information, we do not extract any information from your computer, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

**Registration Forms (Merchants)**  
Our service registration form request merchants to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to send information about our company, and to get in touch with the merchant when necessary. This information is never shared with any outside company or individual.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to send postal mail when necessary.

Merchant information is never used for promotional purposes.

**Mailing List**  
Currently the only information we need is a name and email address. You can opt out of this mailing list at anytime.

**External Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Interneka is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Data Quality/Access**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

For more information about Interneka privacy or information usage policies, e-mail us .
